hubfurniture.com.au 2018-04-18

# Privacy Statement

Privacy Statement
Hub Furniture Lighting Living Pty Ltd (“Hub”) (ABN 11100081767) has adopted the privacy statement set out
below.
Hub values and respects your privacy and recognises your right for personal information to be kept private. This
statement sets out how Hub gathers and manages your personal information that it collects from you when you
use the Website (“Site”).
Visiting the Site
Hub collects information on Site visitors including which sections of the Site are most frequently visited. This
information is used on an aggregated, non-personal basis to enhance and improve the Site.
IP Addresses
Hub’s web server gathers your IP address to assist with the diagnosis of problems or support issues with the Site
and to monitor the legitimate use of the Site.
Collecting Personal Information
In order to provide you with information, to enable you to become a registered user or to purchase goods from
the Site, Hub or a third party may be required to collect your personal information from you. You acknowledge
and consent that in providing personal information to Hub, we may use and or disclose this information for the
express purpose for which it was collected or for a related purpose including facilitating a purchase order,
responding to your request, to enable direct marketing of promotions and marketing of products to you, to enable
third parties to assist us in providing goods and service to you, to seek feedback in relation to client service
satisfaction from you and to regulatory or law enforcement body as required by law.
Storage and Security of Personal Information
Hub takes all reasonable steps to ensure the security of our systems. Any information which we hold about you
is stored on a secure server in a controlled facility. All of Hub’s employees and third party suppliers are obliged to
respect the confidentiality of any personal information held by Hub. Hub is not responsible for events arising from
the unauthorised access of your personal information.
Hub allows you to access your information at any time to keep it accurate and up to date. You are obliged to
notify Hub immediately if there is any unauthorised use of your login or password or any other breach of security.
Cookies
Cookies allow you to use specific parts of the Site and allow you to use functions such as auto login in,
remember your last search etc. Cookies record information about your visit and search activities on the site. Hub
uses this information on an aggregated, non-personal basis to enhance and improve the Site.
Data Transfer
Your personal information may be transferred to a third party contractor or server located outside of Australia. In
providing your personal information to Hub, you consent to this disclosure. Hub transfers your personal
information outside of Australia to third parties on the basis that the recipients are subject to a law or contract
which upholds the principles for fair handling of the information that is consistent with the National Privacy
Principles.

Privacy Changes
From time to time, Hub may review and update its privacy statement. Revised versions will be updated on the
Site.
Contact Us
If you have any questions regarding this privacy statement or you are concerned about the way your personal
information has been handled, you can contact us via the following ways:
Email: privacy@hubfurniture.com.au
Telephone: + 613 9652 1222
Post: The Privacy Officer, Hub Furniture Lighting Living, 63 Exhibition Street, Melbourne VIC 3000, Australia
